Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1969-1993; Accession 1999-A-091
  - Copeland, Roger CSES/ CSMC 331A (Box 36, Folder 1841)
  - Cooper CSES 194b1981 (Box 36, Folder 1842)
  - Bernstein, Howard 1988, 1987, 1978 & 1979 (three folders, bound) (Box 36, Folder 1843)
  - Firk, Frank CSTC 334A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1844)
  - Firk, Frank CSTC 317A 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1845)
  - Chapman, V. & Thompson, D. CSTC/ BR 343b (Box 36, Folder 1846)
  - Kaufman, Frederick CSTD/ SM 347b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1847)
  - Chisholm, Linda CSTC/ CSSM 341b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1848)
  - Phillipy, Patricia CSTC/ SY 342C 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1849)
  - Cooper, Joseph CSES 345b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1850)
  - Cooper CSES 307b1987 (Box 36, Folder 1851)
  - Cooper CSES/ CSBR 284b1985 (Box 36, Folder 1852)
  - Cooper CSES/ CSJE 236b1983 (Box 36, Folder 1853)
  - Cooper CSES 170b (Box 36, Folder 1854)
  - Douglas, Lawrence CSSY/ CC 344b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1855)
  - Douglas, Lawrence SY/ CC 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1856)
  - Porter, Charles CSSY 340b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1857)
  - Wimstatt, Margaret CSSM/ TC 345b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1858)
  - Wimstatt, Margaret CSSM/ CSPC 311b1987 (Box 36, Folder 1859)
  - Greenwald, Bernard CSPC/ TD 344b1989 (Box 36, Folder 1860)
  - Greenwald, Bernard CSPC/ CSBR 318A 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1861)
  - Greenwald CSBK 136A (Box 36, Folder 1862)
  - Greenwald CSTD 58b/ CSMC (Box 36, Folder 1863)
  - Greenwald JE 80A (Box 37, Folder 1864)
  - Harris & Kayton CSMC/ SM 348b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1865)
  - Harris, Melissa & Kayton, Deborah CSDC/ TC 1988 (Box 37, Folder 1866)
  - Rosenheim, Shawn CSMC/ CSES 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1867)
  - Payne, Leigh CSMC/ BK 343b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1868)
  - Plott, Michele CSMC/ CSTC 340b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1869)
  - DeNardis, Lawrence CSMC/ PC 345b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1870)
  - Kaufman CSTD/ SM 347b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1874)
  - Richardson, Robert CSJE/ TD 345b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1875)
  - Ye, Wei Li TD/ JE 342b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1876)
  - Cole, K.C. CSTD 340b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1877)
  - Macy, Jeffrey CSTD/ SM 346b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1878)
  - Zarin, Cynthia TD/ ES 341b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1879)
  - Kerr, Minot CSDC/ TC 344b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1880)
  - French CSCC/ CSTC 284b1985 (Box 37, Folder 1881)
  - Lesser, Guy CSBK 341b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1882)
  - Lesser CSBK 277b1985 (Box 37, Folder 1883)
  - Winnie, Lawrence CSBK/ CSBR 346b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1884)
  - Proto, Neil CSBK/ CSDC 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1885)
  - Proto, Neil CSSM/ PC 327b1988 (Box 37, Folder 1886)
  - Wakeman, Carolyn CSBK 342b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1887)
  - Wakeman, Carolyn CSES/ SY 326b1988 (Box 37, Folder 1888)
  - Browning, Barbara CSBR/ CSJE 347b1989 (Box 37, Folder 1889)
  - Residential College Seminars Course Description Catalogues:f1989- Sp 1990 (no manilla folder) (Box 38, Folder 1890)
  - Misc. Forms & Receipts 1988- 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1891)
  - Graduate Student Forms 1989- 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1892)
  - Appointments, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1893)
  - Masters 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1894)
  - Permission to Teach From Department Heads (Box 38, Folder 1895)
  - Credit To The Major Sp 90 (Box 38, Folder 1896)
  - Master's Letters Sp 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1897)
  - Master's Letters Sp 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1898)
  - Graduate Student Forms 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 1899)
  - Dept. Appointments Fall 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1900)
  - Geyer CSBK/ TC 352A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1901)
  - Moyano CSBR/ TC 351A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1902)
  - Moyano, Maria CSDC/ CSBR 336A 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1903)
  - Ellis CSBR/ PC 350A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1904)
  - Ellis, Deborah CSDC/ CSSM 331A 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1905)
  - Silverman CSBR/ BK 355A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1906)
  - Thomas Rubin CSCC/ BK 354A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1907)
  - Huston CSDC 350A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1908)
  - Wegener CSDC 355A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1909)
  - Klopfer CSDC/ ES 354A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1910)
  - Flink CSTD/ DC 351A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1912)
  - Viehmann, Martha CSMC/ CC 350A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1914)
  - Byler CSPC/ SY 351A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1915)
  - Byler, Charles CSTC/ CSBK 331A 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1916)
  - Boasberg CSPC/ TD 356A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1917)
  - Egan, Daniel CSSY/ BR 353A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1918)
  - Egan, Daniel CSTC/ CSES 302a 1986 (Box 38, Folder 1919)
  - Egan, Daniel CSSY 327b1988 (Box 38, Folder 1920)
  - Munro CSSY/ TC 355A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1921)
  - Blaisdell CSSY/ TD 350A (Box 38, Folder 1922)
  - Wagner, Michael CSSM/ PC 354A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1923)
  - Barkin (Box 38, Folder 1924)
  - Mehan CSSM/ CC 351A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1925)
  - Kane CSES/ MC 351A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1926)
  - Carolan CSTC/ ES 370A 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1927)
  - Henderson CSTC/ TD 363b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1928)
  - Jacoby, Tamar CSTC/ TD 360b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1929)
  - Jacoby, Tamar CSTC/ CSSY 314A 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1930)
  - Jacoby, Tamar CSSY/ CSCC 308A 1986 (Box 38, Folder 1931)
  - Camhi CSES/ BR 360b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1932)
  - Prothero CSES 367b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1933)
  - Lieberman CSES/ SM 363b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1934)
  - Hilibrand CSES/ PC 365b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1935)
  - Berat. Lynn CSSM/ TC 361b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1936)
  - Berat, Lynn CC/ JE 342b1989 (Box 38, Folder 1937)
  - Sanders CSSY/ PC 362b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1938)
  - Cole, Henry PC/ DC 342b1989 (Box 38, Folder 1939)
  - Mehta, J. CSPC/ BK 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1940)
  - Sawislak, K. CSMC/ DC 360b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1941)
  - Sawislak, Karen CSSY/ CSBR 334 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1942)
  - Bell, Wendell CSMC 362b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1943)
  - Bell CSMC/ CSSY 236b1983 (Box 38, Folder 1944)
  - Erlich, Victor CSMC/ SY 364b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1945)
  - Erlich CSMC/ CSSM 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1946)
  - Kasha CSMC 365b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1947)
  - Bell, Neal CSMC/ CC 361b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1948)
  - Scholl, Tim CSJE/ SM 364b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1949)
  - Scholl, Tim CSTD/ CSSY 335A 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1950)
  - Vamos, M. CSJE/ BR 360b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1951)
  - Sullivan, CSJE/ CC 353A (Box 38, Folder 1952)
  - Goldstein, L. CSJE/ SY 365b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1953)
  - Saravelle CSJE/ CC 355A 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1954)
  - Heifetz, Henry CSJE/ CC 360b1990 (Box 38, Folder 1955)
  - Nordstrom, Lou CSTD/ SM 362b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1956)
  - Nordstrom CSCC/ ES (Box 39, Folder 1957)
  - Berkowitz CSTD/ TC 366b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1958)
  - Kalb, Paul CSTD/ DC 365b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1959)
  - Rochberg, Halton CSTD/ BR 364b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1960)
  - Ponet, J. & Berkowitz CSTD/ TC 366b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1961)
  - Meyer CSDC/ TC 367b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1962)
  - Meyer CSDC/ CSPC 243b1983 (Box 39, Folder 1963)
  - Meyer CSDC 216b1982 (Box 39, Folder 1964)
  - Boyd- Bowman CSCC 362b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1965)
  - Girardet CSCC/ SM 366b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1966)
  - Breed CSCC/ SM 367b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1967)
  - Oberdek, K. CSBK/ SM 360b (Box 39, Folder 1968)
  - Seow, Francis CSBK/ SY 366b1990 (Box 39, Folder 1969)
  - Residential College Seminars Course Listings Fall 1990- Sp 1991 (no manilla folder) (Box 39, Folder 1970)
  - Masters Letters Sp 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1971)
  - Appts. Sp 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1972)
  - Dept. Appts. Sp 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1973)
  - Credit to the Majors Sp 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1974)
  - Masters Letters Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1975)
  - Credit to the Major Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1976)
  - Middleton CSBK 374A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1977)
  - Spanier, Ktziah CSBK/ TC 371A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1978)
  - Spiro CSBK 373A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1979)
  - Spiro, Howard CSBK 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1980)
  - Spiro, Howard CSBK 315A 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1981)
  - Howard M. Spiro, M. D. CSBK/ CSMC 267b (Box 39, Folder 1982)
  - Hirshman CSBR/ SM 373A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1983)
  - Rhea Hirshman CSMC 278A 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1984)
  - Kingwell CSBR/ ES 374A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1985)
  - O'Melinn, Liam CSBK/ BR 372A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1986)
  - O'Melinn CSSY/ SM 352A 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1987)
  - O'Melinn CSTD/ CSBK 78b1985 (Box 39, Folder 1988)
  - Dirks, Jacqueline CSDC/ SY 373A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1989)
  - Dirks, Jacqueline CSMC/ CSCC 331A 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1990)
  - Dirks, Jacqueline CSBR/ CSSM 315A 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1991)
  - Meagher CSDC/ CC 374A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1992)
  - Meagher, Robert CSTC/ SM 349bSp 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1993)
  - Policoff CSTD/ PC 375A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1994)
  - Policoff, Stephen CSCC/ CSBR 341bSp 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1995)
  - Policoff, Stephen CSTD/ CSBK 316A Fall 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1996)
  - Policoff, Stephen CSBK/ CSTD 301A Fall 1986 (Box 39, Folder 1997)
  - Hartigan CSTD/ TC 373A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1998)
  - Kaplan CSTD/ PC 374A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1999)
  - Kaplan, Howard CSTD/ CSPC 343bSp 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2000)
  - Kaplan, Howard CSES 323b1988 (Box 39, Folder 2001)
  - Kaplan, Howard CSDC/ CSCC 304A 1986 (Box 39, Folder 2002)
  - Kaplan, Howard CSCC/ CSJE 286A Fall 1985 (Box 39, Folder 2003)
  - Kaplan, Howard CSSM 260bSp 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2004)
  - Kaplan CSBK 240bSp 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2005)
  - Shapiro CSJE/ BR 375A 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2006)
  - Felstiner, Mary JE/ PC Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2007)
  - Honig CSJE/ PC 370A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2008)
  - Huginnie CSMC/ BK 374A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2009)
  - Salgado CSMC/ BK 376A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2010)
  - Meyer CSMC/ TC 375A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2011)
  - Meyer, Stephen CSMC/ CSSY 341bSp 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2012)
  - Sutterlin CSMC/ CC 370A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2013)
  - Sutterlin, James CSPC/ CSTD 332A Fall 1988 (Box 39, Folder 2014)
  - Robinson CSMC/ PC 377A Fall 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2015)
  - Robinson, Ian CSJE/ CSSY Sp 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2016)
  - Ross CSPC 366bSp 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2017)
  - Ross Steven CSSY/ CSES 333A Fall 1988 (Box 40, Folder 2018)
  - Ross CSTD 65b (Box 40, Folder 2019)
  - Ross CSTD 140b (Box 40, Folder 2020)
  - Ross CSSY 85b (Box 40, Folder 2021)
  - Shepherd CSPC/ JE 376A Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2022)
  - Bernstein CSPC/ ES 371A Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2023)
  - Baer/ Abrahamsom CSSY/ CC 372A Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2026)
  - Sellers Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2027)
  - Katzman CSES/ SY 375A Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2028)
  - Koning TC/ MC Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2029)
  - Sharp CSTC/ BR 381b 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2030)
  - Hollander CSTC/ MC 384b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2031)
  - Boonin-Vail CSTC 380b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2032)
  - Krikorian CSSY/ DC 386b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2033)
  - Krikorian CSCC/ BR 371A Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2034)
  - Krikorian ES/ MC 352A Fall 1989 (Box 40, Folder 2035)
  - O. Jones CSSY/ CC383b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2036)
  - Stowe CSSM/ PC 385b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2037)
  - Brockelman CSSM/ BK 386b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2038)
  - Choharis CSSM/ TC 383b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2039)
  - Drayton CSES/CC 384b (Box 40, Folder 2040)
  - Klineberg CSES 388b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2041)
  - Forbes CSES/ CC 386b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2042)
  - Behre CSES/ DC 385b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2043)
  - Herskovits CSMC/ TC 382b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2044)
  - Dietle CSMC/ PC 380b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2045)
  - John Davis CJSE/ TD 381b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2046)
  - Somerville CSJE/ TD 383b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2047)
  - Ryan CJE 387b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2048)
  - Ryan CSJE 192b Sp 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2049)
  - Ad. Davis CSBK/ TC 385b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2050)
  - Solino CSBK/ SY 384b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2051)
  - O=Melinn CSBR/ ES 383b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2052)
  - Fiol- Matta CSBR/ CC 385b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2053)
  - Swinth CSBR/ JE 386b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2054)
  - Brakke CSBR/ ES 380b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2055)
  - Whitehead CSCC/ BK 387b (Box 40, Folder 2056)
  - Lowe CSCC/ SM 380b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2057)
  - Tobin CSDC 384b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2058)
  - Residential College Seminars Catalogues of Course Listings Fall 1991- Sp 1992 (no manilla folder (Box 40, Folder 2059)
  - Mellon Sr. Forums 1991- 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2060)
  - Mellon Reports 1991- 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2061)
  - General A (Box 40, Folder 2062)
  - Berkeley b (Box 40, Folder 2063)
  - Branford C (Box 40, Folder 2064)
  - Calhoun D (Box 40, Folder 2065)
  - Davenport E (Box 40, Folder 2066)
  - Jon. Edws. G (Box 40, Folder 2067)
  - Morse H (Box 40, Folder 2068)
  - Pierson J. (Box 40, Folder 2069)
  - Saybrook K. (Box 40, Folder 2070)
  - Silliman L. (Box 40, Folder 2071)
  - Stiles M. (Box 40, Folder 2072)
  - Trumbull N. (Box 40, Folder 2073)
  - Timothy Dwight P (Box 40, Folder 2074)
  - Graduate Student Forms Sp 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2075)
  - Master=s Letters Sp 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2076)
  - Credit to Major Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2077)
  - Master=s Letters Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2078)
  - Graduate Student Forms Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2079)
  - Booklet Sp 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2080)
  - Allotments-- by college or term 1991- 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2081)
  - Kamensky CSBK/ SM 391A Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2082)
  - Matos CSBK/ CC 390A Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2083)
  - Matos BK/ DC Fall 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2084)
  - Matos, Felix CSBK/ PC 325b Sp 1988 (Box 40, Folder 2085)
  - Scheffler CSBK/ MC 393b Fall 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2086)
  - Zdanys CSBR 384b Sp 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2087)
  - Zdanys CSBR/ JE 340b Sp 1989 (Box 40, Folder 2088)
  - Zdanys, Jonas CSBR/ PC 323b Sp 1988 (Box 40, Folder 2089)
  - Zdanys, Jonas CSBR/ CSDC 299b Sp 1986 (Box 40, Folder 2090)
  - Zdanys CSBR 280b Sp 1985 (Box 40, Folder 2091)
  - Pliner CSCC/ SM 392A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2092)
  - Markiewitz CSTD/ CC 391A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2093)
  - O=Connor CSTD/ CC 393A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2094)
  - Guida CSTD/ JE 390b Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2095)
  - Shapiro CSJE/ BR 391A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2096)
  - Crewdson CSMC/ TD 392A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2097)
  - Crewdson, Gregory CSBR/ SM 370A Fall 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2098)
  - Anderson CSMC/ BK 394A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2099)
  - Arenson CSPC/ TD 394A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2100)
  - Dull CSPC/ DC 391A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2101)
  - Dull CSMC 222b (Box 41, Folder 2102)
  - Murray CSPC/ SM 393A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2103)
  - Scharfs CSSY/ BR 390A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2104)
  - Bell CSSY/ TD 395A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2105)
  - M. Bell CSSY/ TD 395A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2106)
  - Bell, Michael CSJE/ BK 351A Fall 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2107)
  - Michaelson CSSM/ BR 395A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2108)
  - Giliberti CSES/ TC 390A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2109)
  - LaRegin ES Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2110)
  - Marguiles CSES/ SY 393A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2111)
  - Marguiles CSDC/ SY 371A Fall 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2112)
  - Waterman CSTC/ TC 397A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2113)
  - Waterman CSTC 37bSp 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2114)
  - Thorne CSTC/ PC 396A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2115)
  - Vacca CSTC/ DC 394A Fall 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2116)
  - Seidman, Rachel CSTC/ PC 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2117)
  - Dorsey, Kurk CSTC/ JE 400b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2118)
  - Klausner, Lewis CSTC/ PC 403b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2119)
  - Corn, Alfred CSES/ SM 406b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2120)
  - Corn, Alfred CSSM/ CSCC 295b Sp 1986 (Box 41, Folder 2121)
  - Corn CSSM 86b (Box 41, Folder 2122)
  - Corn CSSM 110b (Box 41, Folder 2123)
  - Fortes, Stephan CSES/ SY 424b Sp 1993 (Box 41, Folder 2124)
  - Fortes, Stephan CSMC/ SM 404b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2125)
  - Fortes CSBK 382b Sp 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2126)
  - Flick CSSm 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2127)
  - Sifuentes, Benigno CSSM/ BK 400b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2128)
  - Fernald, Anne CSSY/ ES 405b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2129)
  - Gill, Ralph CSSY/ ES 407b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2130)
  - Pickford, H. & Spargo, Cliff CSMC/ SM 402b Spring 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2131)
  - Belgrad, Daniel CSMC/ ES 403b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2132)
  - Brescia, Raymond CSMC/ TD 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2133)
  - Coons, Christopher CSPC/ MC 405b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2134)
  - Perotta CSJE/ SM 403b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2135)
  - Perrotta CSJE/ SM 384b Sp 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2136)
  - Minwalla, Framji CSJE/ ES 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2137)
  - Schwartzberg, Steven CSTD/ SY 400b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2138)
  - Ouweleen, Mark CSDC/ SY 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2139)
  - Nordstrom, Lou CSCC/ ES Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2140)
  - Wasink, Craig CSCC/ JE 402b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2141)
  - Barnhouse, Dorothy CSCC/ ES Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2142)
  - Woolf, Jeffrey CSDC/ CC 403b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2143)
  - Bay, Mia CSBR/ CC 400b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2144)
  - Mao, Douglas CSBR/ TD 403b (Box 41, Folder 2145)
  - Zdanys, Jonas CSBR 404b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2146)
  - Green, Amy CSBR/ CC 401b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2147)
  - Kurzweil, Allen CSBR/ DC 402b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2148)
  - Abrams, Elizabeth CSBK/ CC 406b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2149)
  - Pearsall, Cornelia CSBK/ TD 402b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2150)
  - Townsend, Gretchen CSBK/ PC 407b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2151)
  - Jones, Barbara CSBK/ BR 405b Sp 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2152)
  - b. Jones CSTD/ MC 385b Sp 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2153)
  - Jones CSTD/ BR 354A Fall 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2154)
  - Jones, Barbara CSJE/ DC Fall 1988 (Box 41, Folder 2155)
  - Residential College Seminars Course Listings Catalogs Fall 1992- 1993 (no manilla envelope) (Box 42, Folder 2156)
  - Graduate Student Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2157)
  - Budgets Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2158)
  - Master=s Letters Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2159)
  - Appts & Credit to the Major Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2160)
  - Expense Reports 1992- 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2161)
  - Ferguson CSBK/ SY Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2162)
  - Sharp CSBK/ TC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2163)
  - Simmons CSBK/ TD Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2164)
  - Simmons CSBK/ PC 383b Sp 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2165)
  - Simmons, R. BK & CC Sp 1989 (Box 42, Folder 2166)
  - Simmons, Robert CSBK/ MC 321b Sp 1988 (Box 42, Folder 2167)
  - Simmons, Robert R. CSES/ CSMC 300A Fall 1986 (Box 42, Folder 2168)
  - Simmons, Robert CSBK/ CSMC 288A Fall 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2169)
  - Cappel CSCC/ SM Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2170)
  - VosFellman CSCC/ SM Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2171)
  - Garvin CSDC/ SM Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2172)
  - Garvin, Alexander CSDC 292A Fall 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2173)
  - Garvin, CSDC 227A Fall 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2174)
  - Garvin CSPC 152b (Box 42, Folder 2175)
  - Saxon CSDC/ TC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2176)
  - Singer CSDC/ MC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2177)
  - Singer CSMC/ DC 391A Fall 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2178)
  - Dorothy Singer MC 20b (Box 42, Folder 2179)
  - Martz CSSY/ SY Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2180)
  - Martz, Louis CSSY/ CSPC 346b Sp 1989 (Box 42, Folder 2181)
  - Martz, CSSY/ CSCC 225A Fall 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2182)
  - Cohen, M. CSTD/ JE Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2183)
  - Arenson CSJE/ BR Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2184)
  - Andreopoulos CSPC/ ES Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2185)
  - Andreopoulos Fall 1990 (Box 42, Folder 2186)
  - Rischin CSPC/ BR Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2187)
  - Casas CSSY/ BK Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2188)
  - Garrett CSES/ CC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2189)
  - Jackson CSES/ CC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2190)
  - Jackson CSSY 284b Sp 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2191)
  - (Jackson, 1980) (Box 42, Folder 2192)
  - Jackson, ES workshop (Box 42, Folder 2193)
  - Jackson, CSES/ CSSY 94b (Box 42, Folder 2194)
  - Jackson CSSY 143b (Box 42, Folder 2195)
  - Poats CSES/ PC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2196)
  - Shurtz CSES/ CC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2197)
  - Smith, W. CSES/ SM Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2198)
  - Collier CSTC/ SM Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2199)
  - Collier CSTC/ DC 362bSp 1990 (Box 42, Folder 2200)
  - Slater CSTC/ PC Fall 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2201)
  - Holloway, Jonathan TC/CC 422b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2202)
  - Zucker, John ES/ PC 420b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2203)
  - Zucker CSDC/ MC 383b Sp 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2204)
  - Zucker, John CSTC/ SY 354A Fall 1989 (Box 42, Folder 2205)
  - Zucker, John CSSY/ CSJE 311b Sp 1987 (Box 42, Folder 2206)
  - Zucker, John W. CSSM/ TD 322b Sp 1988 (Box 42, Folder 2207)
  - Bruzelius, Margaret CSES/ SY 423b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2208)
  - Ginsberg, Harvey CSES/ DC 425b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2209)
  - Appold, Kenneth SM/ JE 421 Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2210)
  - Maynard, Gary CSSM/ BR 420b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2211)
  - Rodgers, Peter CSSM/ BR 426b Sp 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2212)
  - Koh, Hesung TC/ BK 423b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2213)
  - Koh, Hesung Chun CSES/ SM 343G Sp 1989 (Box 43, Folder 2214)
  - Koh, Hesung CSDC/ CSSM Sp 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2215)
  - Koh, Hesung Chun CSTD/ CSMC 306A Fall 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2216)
  - Hesung Chun Koh CSJE/ CSCC 277A Fall 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2217)
  - Koh CSTD/ CSJE 231A Fall 1982 (Box 43, Folder 2218)
  - Koh CSJE 208A Fall 1981 (Box 43, Folder 2219)
  - Koh CSTD/ CSDC 96b 1977 (Box 43, Folder 2220)
  - Scott, Stephanie CSSY/ BK 426b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2221)
  - Scott, Stephanie CSDC/ SY 404b Sp 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2222)
  - Stuart, Barbara CSSY/ BR 422b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2223)
  - Cohen. Lisa CSMC/ DC 421b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2224)
  - Cohen, L. CSMC/ SY Fall 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2225)
  - Eicher, Clay MC/ BK 420b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2226)
  - Eicher, Clay CSBK/ PC 404b Sp 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2227)
  - Eicher/ Henderson CSTC/ TD 363b Sp 1990 (Box 43, Folder 2228)
  - Tambiah, Yasmin CSMC/ BR 423b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2229)
  - Baldwin, John JE/ TD 424b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2230)
  - Farnam, James DC/ TC 420b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2231)
  - Farnam CSBK/ SY 380b Sp 1991 (Box 43, Folder 2232)
  - Farnam, James CSPC/ SY 347G Sp 1989 (Box 43, Folder 2233)
  - Faram, James CSMC/ ES 322b Sp 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2234)
  - MacDonnell DC/ PC 422b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2235)
  - Lepore, Jill TD/ PC 423b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2236)
  - Connelly, Bernadine CSCC/ SM 424b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2237)
  - Hefti, Susan BR/ TD 421b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2238)
  - Hefti, Susan CSES/ TC 402b Sp 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2239)
  - Levin, Douglas CSBR/ SY 425b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2240)
  - Lober, Doug BK/ ES 421b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2241)
  - Lober, Doug BK/ ES 421b Sp 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2242)
  - Lober, Douglas CSBR/ DC 406b Sp 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2243)
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1993-2002; Accession 2007-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  Scope and Contents
  Each box contains a full academic year of course files labeled with the term and year, course number, and instructor name. Within each box, folders are arranged in alpha order by residential college sponsorship (indicated by the inclusion of the college's initials in the course number, e.g. CSBK stands for College Seminar Berkeley). Folders for fall term precede those of spring, but are found in the same college section. Each folder contains a complete course proposal, instructor appointment form, copy of the I-9, and student evaluations (two kinds -- the program form and the Registrar's on line evaluations). Multiple pocket files for any instructor are grouped together with the most recent term in front (this is because previous student evaluations are reviewed when reconsidering a course for approval).
  - A Handbook for Coordinators of Residential College Seminars, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1993 and Spring 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Kerbel, Michael -BK/DC 430a--Fall, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Kerbel, Michael -CSBK/MC 395a, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)